Lewes
I know Daniel is a bit of a jerk
and doesn't deserve your help
but my parents are getting old
if they
As long as they don't bleed me dry
to help Daniel
I can provide for them
They're your parents after all
I can't just ignore them
Lewes
You're the best
You
This is illegal
Brian
Let's talk this out
What are you doing
Talk nicely
Like you deserve it
Your three days are up
Where's the money
The money
Please give me two more days
I promise I'll pay you back
Bullshit
You've said that a million times
If you can't pay
By the rules
we chop off your hand
Boys
Hold him down
No
You can't chop off my son's hand
He's not even married yet
Please have mercy
He's our only son
Cut the crap
A debt must be paid
It's only right